Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION.
Clear the way! Get out of the way!
Answer my questions.
That you've saved my life doesn't matter,
I can still kill you.
What are you doing here?
Did you kill the Governor?
What Governor? What are you talking about?
As a Turk, what are you doing here?
You nearly killed him.
Ertuğrul's son Osman.
What the hell are you doing?
How did you come up here?
Ertuğrul Bey's son, the famous Osman, huh?
He is skillful like his father.
They say, "A wolf's offspring becomes
another wolf."
Do what you have to do.
I'll take care of him.
Job 26:7 [ Bible verse ]
"He puts north in nothingness."
"He drops the earth in...
nothingness."
148:3
"Glorify him."
"The sun and the moon,
all the gleaming stars."
104:6
"He wore the headwaters like a dress."
"And the water was standing
on the top of the mountains"
Absolute thanks to my Lord.
Allah is the greatest.
We also need to find
what our master mentioned.
I've found it.
IN THE NAME OF ALLAH THE MERCIFUL.
"Indeed, We have given you,
[O Muhammad], a clear conquest"
Surah Al-Fath [48:1]
Thank Allah.
Now that the Governor is dead,
there must be a panic.
We don't have much time. Come on,
hurry up. We need to take him out now.
Ya Bismillah! ( in the name of Allah.)
You couldn't protect your Governor.
You turned his castle into
a grave for him.
Damn you, Commanders.
None of you have been like Osman.
Damn it.
Answer me!
How could you not take precautions?
How could you not!
In this castle, there is no traitor
who means to kill our Governor.
We were his sons.
We would risk our lives for him.
We'll question everyone in the castle.
We'll make everyone talk.
Where was the Governor?
With whom was he?
We'll learn everything.
He was in his room.
I sent Helen to his room to call him.
After I notified our Governor with
our offer, he took action.
But, before I went into his room, I saw
Ertuğrul's son Osman leaving his room.
What did you say?
- Are you sure that he was Osman?
- Yes, sir.
It was Ertuğrul's son Osman.
Osman...
Search the whole castle right away,
Andreas.
Get all the Commanders into the act!
Search for the whole castle!
Come on.
I hear footsteps.
Don't worry.
He'll wake up soon.
He has a heart that could dare
all the world.
He'll take care of himself.
Let's go.
You're entrusted to Allah.
Let's go!
Come on, come on, hurry up!
Run! Hurry up!
Inform the Commanders.
Osman is in the castle.
I promise you I will find Osman,
and we will be settled down.
I told you the stars would
help us tonight.
Commander Kalonoz, Commander Kalonoz!
Osman is in the Sofia's starry room!
- Starry room?
- I'll catch him, Sofia.
What is Osman doing there?
The holy entrustment!
You killed our Governor, you bastard!
The killer of the Governor
is the most innocent one of you.
Run! Catch Osman!
Catch him before he exits the castle!
Damn it, we missed him!
The Governor is dead!
Where are you, my Bey?
My Bey.
My Bey, drink water.
Catch your breath.
I worried about you when the bells ringed.
The governor is dead, I am held
responsible for it.
What are you talking about, my Bey?
We need to find somewhere to hide
immediately.
Let's go to Mario's place, my Bey.
You thought it well. Don't let anyone
stop you, kill them all!
- Okay.
- Let's go!
They took the holy entrustment and the
treasure!
Damn it!
Forgive my sins, god.
Inform Master Yannis right away.
Sofia, Master Yannis would make both
of us pay for this.
How could we explain this to Master
Yannis, huh?
We couldn't enjoy the governor's
death, now we sorrow for this.
Osman.
I'll bite your lungs out with my teeth.
Osman!
Apparently, no one saw us.
Nobody is around.
I'll pray to thank to Allah when we
arrive in our city.
You need to depart early in the morning.
Won't you come?
The war has just started, daughter.
The ones who serve to the devil will
take action.
The Governor has been killed, things will
go crazy here.
Do you think Osman is okay?
What if he couldn't get out?
Thank my Lord.
We have found Ahi Evren's treasure, which
was kept by the enemy.
We have the blessed treasure of
Ahmad Yasawi.
Thank Lord.
I wonder, my Bey.
Who do you think killed the Governor?
I don't know, brother.
I don't know.
However, I know something.
The Governor was killed by his closest ones.
You are right, my Bey.
Governor nursed vipers in his bosom.
Why did they kill him?
Because he made peace with us.
They couldn't accept this.
They want to end the peace and
fight again.
Who are those bastards, my Bey?
As they arranged such an ignominious
assassinate...
It must be a secret organization.
A secret organization that is everywhere
in Bithynia
They took advantage of the fact that my
father is in Konya.
- We should send men to the tribe, my Bey.
- Kalonoz must have done it already.
Their aim is to disorder the tent
by using me.
My brothers, we are under attack
from two sides.
The woman who masqueraded as a
priestess...
She is our salvation.
If we find her, we'll find both
the murderer of the Governor and...
the traitors in the castle.
- Did you that devil?
- The ground swallowed him up, dajjal Turk!
Unless you find Osman, we can't breathe
in this land!
I'll find him.
Swear to god, I'll find and kill him
myself!
It's not easy to find him.
- He must come with his will.
- How?
He is a Turk who risked his life
for the Governor.
If we capture someone from his blood...
he'll give in to save him.
Devil took the possession of the whole
castle tonight.
Sometimes you need to get help from
the devil to keep up.
We'll take an entrustment from Dündar Bey.
And that entrustment will make Osman
be revealed.
And because of Osman, the tent
will be troubled.
I'll send my most trusted man.
Dündar Bey is going to be mad about this.
And the agreement will be infringed.
Ertuğrul's son Osman...
who killed our Governor has infringed
the agreement.
Everyone should hear and believe that
Osman has committed this murder.
Everyone should know how Kayıs treat
their friends.
- Can I, Uncle?
- Come in, Gündüz Bey.
Is there any news from Osman?
We searched everywhere, uncle.
But, nothing is up.
I don't understand what his aim is.
Sometimes he saves the day...
sometimes he spoils the day.
This has gone too far, Dündar Bey.
Ertuğrul Ghazi should know what happened.
You should send a letter that tells what
happened in the tent, Dündar Bey.
You need to report Osman's situation.
My aunt is right. What would we do if my
father came to the tent and asked...
where Osman is?
Ahh, Osman, ah.
Look what you've done to me.
But, you gave me no option.
You didn't.
- Selamun Aleikum, Dündar Bey.
- Aleikum Selam, Bamsı Bey.
- Here, sit down.
- Thank you.
Long live, Dündar Bey.
Osman, Dündar Bey, where is he?
It's been a while, but Osman is not
around.
The enemy is waiting for a gap.
What if they hunt Osman down, like my
Aybars?
We were going to ask you, Bamsı Bey.
I am not Bey, son.
The Bey is Dündar Bey.
He needs to know what is going on.
If something happens to Osman, how can you
explain it to my Ertuğrul Bey, huh?
Huh?
Brother Gündüz?
Uncle Dündar?
Bey.
I wish my Ertuğrul Bey had come so that...
the tent could be in order.
Send Alps (men) for Osman, Gündüz Bey.
They shall not come back without his trace.
Will you send the letter, my Bey?
My Bey, I'm talking to you.
What should I tell to my brother, huh?
What should I tell? Should I tell him that
I couldn't take care of Osman?
Won't he ask me that how will you deal
with the tent...
while you can't even take care of Osman?
Is Governor Yorgopolos dead?
Yes, sir.
So, why are you silent as the snow on the
Olympios Mountains, Megela?
Sir, the runner that Sofia sent brought
you a letter.
Read it.
Read, Megela, read!
What is written in the letter?
Sir...
The holy entrustment and the treasure are
stolen from the sorcery room.
It happened in the Yorgopolos' scene.
Who did know the place of the room that
the secret is hidden, huh?
How did they learn this, Megela, how?
- Who did this?
- Ertuğrul Ghazi's son Osman.
A shepherd Turk has spoiled everything!
Osman, Osman, Osman...
Get my horse ready, we are going to
Kulucahisar Castle
Yes, sir.
What happened to this store?
Everything's messed up.
Ugh!
You can't even rely on your helpmate.
God damn you all!
Who are you?
What are you looking for?
Don't take it personally, man.
You'll work for us today.
Let's finish this.
Okay, my Bey.
The carriage is ready.
It is time to depart.
They'll wait for you outside of the
castle.
I charged the soldiers in the gate.
If someone asks you something,
don't talk.
Those soldiers will save you.
May Allah help you, Dursun Bey.
May my Lord make you the victorious
in this cruel land.
Thank you, daughter.
Thank you.
I respectfully kiss my
master's blessed hands.
I hope he wouldn't forsake his
prayers from this poor man.
Tell him we need his favour and breath.
Master Dursun.
Is there any news about Osman?
He is missing, for now.
He is Osman, son of Ertuğrul.
No one could know where
and when he could show up.
- May Allah help you, Dursun Bey.
- Amen.
May Allah help you.
Folks!
Last night, our governor,
Yorgopolos was murdered!
May God take him to his heaven.
The killer of our governor is Osman Bey,
son of Ertuğrul from the Kayıs!
The killer of our governor is Osman Bey!
We know that the killer is in our castle.
Whoever helps him,
dies with the whole family!
Our governor, Yorgopolos was murdered!
Driver, stop!
- What's in the cart?
- It's extra-virgin olive oil.
Good, open it so we can see then.
It can't have sunlight,
they will be wasted, soldier.
- It's olive oil-
- Enough!
- You'll make me starve in winter.
- I said open it!
Please, I'm going to be
hungry with my children.
Just leave it, are we going to find
Osman in a barrel of olive oil?
- Come on.
- What are you waiting for, move!
May God spare you for your children.
Open the gate!
Thank you, my Allah! Victory is ours!
We are near the church, my Bey.
Shall we come with you?
You do as I ordered, I will enter
the church alone, I will see you soon.
Greetings, Priest.
Welcome to the house of God,
strong warrior of Jesus Christ.
I wish everyone...
... could have the strength to handle
the hardships like our Lord Jesus Christ.
All prophets are embodiments of faith.
It is not easy to be
like our Lord Jesus Christ.
How lucky you are, Master Priest, to spend
your life in a sanctuary like this...
... away from all the
sins, the filth out there.
- This is the first time I see you here.
- Because it's my first time here.
Do you know the face of
everyone from your community?
Our church community is fewer in this age.
Most of them chose to become
a Muslim because of the Turks.
Old people usually visit here, but when
I see younglings, I don't let them go.
- That's why I couldn't recognize you.
- I'm looking for a nun.
She is a very important person for me.
If you tell me her name, maybe I can help.
I don't know her name.
How could I help you
if you don't know her name?
Black eyebrows, hazel eyes...
... about this height.
Son, there must be so many
nuns with these descriptions...
What is that secret of her that
made you chase after this nun?
I owe her my life.
I'd like to pay my debt.
Does she have little freckles on her face?
Yes.
You're talking about our church's mary
Nevodaka.
She lives in a shrine out of the city.
I will describe the place for you.
Are you sure?
Look, son. Listen to me carefully now.
Burçin.
Enough!
Don't you see the rage
inside you poisons you too?
First Aybars, now his men. Who knows to
what trouble he dragged them now.
This tent lost its soul,
it's happiness because of him.
Who knows how many men
will die because of him, Aygül!
And you are still worried
about him. Thinking about him.
Don't you know how Osman
is poisoning you in the first place?
One day, you will also be in
big trouble because of him.
I know you are hurt.
You feel the pain in your bones.
But you put the blame on Osman,
forgetting about the will of Allah.
I will regard the trouble coming
from Osman as an honour!
You should know that.
Of course, I know that.
My Aybars is a martyr.
But this doesn't explain
Osman's recklessness!
No need to talk more, if your heart burns
like mine does now, you will understand.
Good day to you!
Burçin Hatun! Burçin Hatun!
Don't come.
There, Dündar's daughter, let's finish
this before the guards notice anything.
Come on.
You still hate Osman.
Don't forget that he went to
avenge the man you loved.
He took my lover from me, Aygül.
You are still talking about revenge.
He will burn your heart
just like he has burnt mine.
What do you want?
What are you doing here?
Osman killed our governor.
He is trapped in the castle like a rat. We
need bait to lure him out of his hole.
And that bait is you, Aygül Hatun!
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
With the Almighty Allah's 99 names,
who creates everything with "be"...
... who fills our hearts with faith.
Brave men of the Great Oğuz.
You all know about the
circumstances in Bithynia.
These lands that we come in with
my brother, Ertuğrul Gazi's leadership...
... hide their fruitful face from us.
It can't carry our weight anymore.
After all this time, both our tents
and our herds grew in number.
There are many problems appearing
in every tent, every tribe.
Some of us are far from the water,
some of us lack the pasture.
And there are bandits,
caravan ambushers, too.
Because of all these reasons, we have been
searching for a remedy for our troubles.
This remedy is alliance.
[Man 2] That's right.
Thus, we have signed a trade
agreement...
... with our neighbour Yorgopolos,
the Governor of Kulucahisar.
Both them and we will be the winners.
Our goods will be sold in Yenipazar
too, in addition to Söğüt.
What is it, Samsa Bey? You don't seem
to be happy with the results.
Dündar Bey, you say my brother but...
... Ertuğrul Gazi didn't come to
this land calculating incomes.
And he brought us to strike to the
infidels' hearts, not to loot.
Moreover, we've come here to put the
world in order under the wolf banner...
... not to ride caravans!
Also, we can't be friends with infidels.
Brave Bey of Kayı!
I know how you are thrilled when
you hear about the war and fight.
But don't you forget that lands
can be taken with weapons but...
... order can not be
established with weapons.
Order needs coin, wisdom, and skill.
Samsa wants nothing but war, Dündar Bey.
You need order, not war, Nizam Bey.
Ovens become home, homes
become tents, tents become a country.
I've told you so many times to
let us marry you, you didn't want it.
I have been fighting since
I put this black weapon on my belt.
I called bed to eagle nests,
I called blanket to the sky.
I became friends with
hawks, allied with wolves.
I know about your greatness
and virtue, Dündar Bey.
But the only friend or lover
of Samsa, who can't stand still...
... when he hears about fighting,
is this weapon.
Let it be known like this.
I've made my promise, I made my
oaths, my marriage is with this.
And my wedding is with death.
Just because we've formed
an alliance doesn't mean...
... we've left our weapons
like that, Samsa Bey.
Don't you worry, our agreement with
the governor will bring peace to everyone.
There is no peace in a place where
we aren't present Gündüz Bey.
Haven't you figured it out yet?
You blow like the wind and
help us breathe, welcome, Alişar Bey.
Thank you, but we didn't
hear good news, Dündar Bey.
You made an agreement with the governor
without informing the banner lord.
All these tribes, tents, how
did you manage to settle here?
Don't you know I am the shadow
of the Sultan in these lands?
Don't you worry, Alişar Bey.
We surely do not forget
about the order, the respect.
Your door is not the door of wrongs...
... but the door of
rightfulness, Alişar Bey.
We were going to knock on your door after
we are cleaned from our flaws but...
... you were ahead of us.
Let me go! I will see Dündar Bey!
What is going on there?
- Dündar Bey!
- Burçin!
Burçin, my girl! Burçin, my girl!
- What is it? What happened to you?
- Who did this to you?
Drink water. You should
drink water. Who laid their hands on you?
Father! Andreas, commander of Kalonoz.
- They kidnapped Aygül.
- What are you talking about, girl?
How dare them?
Where did they kidnap her, speak!
They ambushed us while
we were doing laundry, my Bey.
They abducted Aygül,
then let me go so I can tell you.
What do they want? Speak, girl.
What do they want?
Osman. They want Osman.
They ask for you for this reason.
- Osman?
- Osman killed the governor.
They are searching for him in the castle.
They took Aygül hostage to find Osman.
My Osman, my Osman went
to the castle to find Aybars' killers.
Dündar Bey, clearly Osman has something,
that's why they are searching for him.
We should go to the castle
before anything happens to Aygül!
Gündüz, you prepare for war with the Beys,
we are going to the castle with Bamsı Bey.
If we don't come back from that castle...
Leave no stone unturned,
leave no shoulder with a head.
I told you, we can't be friends with
infidels. No time to wait, I'm coming too.
You know the best about
the infidels, let's go then.
Dündar Bey.
Where are you going
without the banner lord?
We should take our precautions
first, inform our Sultan.
We wash honour with life,
and blood with blood.
I don't have time to wait.
You do your duty as the banner lord...
... and I will do what needs to
be done as a father and an uncle.
Excuse us.
Look at this hunter of Kayı, Osman...
... I've never seen him
miss his target in our hunts.
He must have tracked
the killer of Aybars carefully.
Let's see what is going to happen now.
Our way is clear from now on.
The information we will get
from the places we will go to...
... will lead us to my
brother Aybar's killers.
Osman, son of Ertuğrul Bey!
I know you are in the
castle and you can hear me!
And I know you killed the governor!
Aygül!
We have witnesses!
We have the daughter of Dündar Bey, Aygül!
I give you one last chance to surrender!
Surrender to Commander Kalonoz now, or the
daughter of Dündar Bey will be killed!
We also send word to Dündar Bey, he will
come to the castle for his daughter!
If you don't surrender, we will
also kill him when he comes!
Tell Osman to come and surrender.
Get up!
Osman! Don't you surrender, Osman!
Shut your mouth!
My Bey, this is not the time for
anger, we need to act now.
Osman this is your last warning from me!
Get up! Get up!
Come here! Osman!
Surrender to Commander Kalonoz now!
If you don't, Aygül's beautiful head
will be removed from her body!
Move! Move!
They may not call me Osman,
son of Ertuğrul anymore...
... if I don't make
this castle their graves.
- What are we going to do my Bey?
- Now is the time to take heads!
We will make these lands
graves to those infidels!
Listen to me carefully.
My husband, Yorgopolos...
Was not just a governor of this castle,
he was the protector of all of us.
But we couldn't protect him, we've
lost him to a treacherous murder.
We will arrange the funeral
ceremony tomorrow.
Has everyone in the region been informed?
Messengers are on their way, ma'am.
This means the start of a
never-ending war with the Turks.
Maximize the precautions
in the entire castle.
Start working to find volunteers
to fight on our side.
I can not even breathe before I take my
husband's revenge from the Turks.
And you, Kalonoz,
I appoint you as my deputy.
Also with the privilege of
using all the power that I have.
I assure you that I will
be worthy of your trust.
You can leave.
Now, speak to me Kalonoz.
What do you think you are doing?
How dare you enter my tent and
kidnap my daughter, like a jackal?
I'm Dündar Bey, son of Süleyman Şah!
Who will protect you from my wrath?
Who will?
Your stone walls? Your iron doors?
The soldiers you put behind those
doors? Who?
Bring me my daughter, now!
Are you threating me in
my own castle, Dündar Bey?
Not in your castle, in the castle
of my friend Yorgopolos.
I'm warning you, Kalonoz.
Threatening is for the weak.
Is Yorgopolos, who I saw as a father, in
a coffin because he was your friend?
Commander! If you have
something to say, say it right away.
Don't mumble.
Osman killed him.
Osman, nephew of Dündar
Bey, friend of Yorgopolos!
The governor would be in a coffin
earlier if we hadn't had Osman...
... when we came for agreement.
We know Osman is in the castle.
If he is innocent, we would
like him to prove it.
We would have done everything
to Aygül, if we had bad intentions.
If you hurt Aygül, I'll burn Kulucahisar
to the ground.
I'll burn it!
Let me go!
Move!
Andreas!
Let the lady go.
My Aygül! My girl!
Are you okay? Did they hurt you?
I'm okay, father.
These bastards don't
have the guts to touch me.
If they had the guts, instead of
blaming Osman...
...they would look for
the governor's killer.
I trusted Osman.
So did my husband.
He granted him privileges no one had.
My husband's killer is Osman, Aygül.
There are witnesses!
Osman! Unless Osman surrenders...
... you, your father, Kayı's Beys,
no one gets out of this castle alive!
- Kalonoz!
- Yes sir.
Until Osman comes, put them all
in the dungeon.
You've shown Byzantine's ugly face, Sofia.
You've shown it.
Are trying to use Osman as an excuse and
ruin our deal with the governor?
Osman is not in this castle, we all
know that.
I see, that it wasn't about Osman, it
was about me.
If we get hurt...
... all of the Turkish tents will be
your nightmare.
Know that.
If you'll burn the whole Kulucahisar for
a single hair of your daughter...
...I'll kill all of the Turkish Tents for
a single drop of the governor's blood.
-Take them out!
-Get them! All of them!
Osman!
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name
of Allah, the beneficent, the merciful)
May it heal you.
My Allah may your valiants be victorious
against the enemy.
Amen.
Inform all the women, all the Alps in
the Tent.
Let the war begin. They must be prepared.
We can make a move any second.
Zöhre Hatun, will we get moving?
We're Turkish women.
We learned to fight from our men.
You were making a lot of noise. Now
talk, Dündar Bey.
You didn't believe Osman was in the
castle.
Look, he's here with us, looking
like a warrior.
I got what I wanted.
I made Osman come into my lap.
What came into your lap is death, Sofia.
Let them go, or everyone dies.
You killed my husband and lots of
my soldiers.
Let him go!
Isn't the blood you spilt enough for
you, Osman?
I keep my promises.
Without taking my nephew Osman with
me, I'm going nowhere. Know that.
Relax, Dündar Bey.
Osman will be on trial in a fair court,
with your judges in it.
Kayı's Beys will also be in this court.
We're after the truth, not spilling blood.
Sofia is right, Dündar Bey.
If we were in the same situation, we
would do the same.
Bamsı Bey.
Do you know what you're talking about?
Where will we go without taking Osman?
My heart is convinced.
A fair court should be established
for everyone's good.
Soldiers! Put your spears down.
Osman!
Uncle!
Go.
Bamsı Bey is right.
Soldiers! Give Dündar Bey his weapons.
And escort them to the exit.
And take Osman to the dungeon.
Osman has been caught! He's in the castle!
Hurry up, come on!
-Hurry up, hurry!
-It's almost done. Keep your eyes open.
Osman Bey! You couldn't protect your
brother!
How could you let him die? How could you?
Answer my questions! I don't care if you
saved me, I'll kill you!
Did you kill the governor?
What governor? What killing?
Shouldn't I be the one who's asking this?
While I was saving Yorgopolos' life...
... you were wandering around
as a useless castle commander.
The assassination attempt was also
a trick, wasn't it?
You Turks were behind this.
Now tell me. What were you doing in the
governor's room disguised as a soldier?
I entered the castle to look for the
ones who were trying to...
... kill the governor and my uncle.
But I was late.
Besides, why would I kill the governor?
He accepted the deal.
You were the only one who didn't
accept it.
If there is someone to be questioned,
it's you Kalonoz.
Why did you kill our governor?
While both the betrayal and the devilry
spreads from the castle you're...
... commanding, are you blaming me?
While you were escaping from the room
you killed the governor in...
... my soldiers saw you.
You're wrong, Kalonoz. Poor governor
fell in front of me.
When I looked up, I saw two shadows.
Shadows, huh.
- So there were more than one.
- Yes.
The governor was taken by surprise.
If they can get that close to him, they
must be someone he knew.
How do you know?
Because he was drowned.
Enough with your nonsense!
You know I'm telling the truth.
I'm not the killer.
Everything will come to light in the
court.
And with great pleasure, I'll rip your
head from your body.
Osman Bey.
I don't know what the court will decide.
But...
... you better believe, that I'll find
the killers.
The dead, can't find anything.
Osman.
Lock the door, don't let anyone inside!
You called me, Madam.
You've thought this through. Osman will
only talk this way.
We should remove his nails, teeth.
He shall feel the pain.
I don't think we can make Osman talk
by torturing him.
-There is no other way, Madam.
-There is.
If Osman managed to get the holy
entrustments...
... he's collaborating with our biggest
enemy.
Someone like him won't surrender
to pain, Helen.
If Osman appears in court, governor's
death will be doubtful, Madam.
-We can't let that happen.
-Osman won't appear in court, Helen.
He'll escape from the dungeon.
Will we get him out of the dungeon?
No, he'll escape by himself.
Osman is smart enough to take precaution
before surrendering.
And he's not alone in the castle.
It's impossible for him to take the
treasure alone.
Do you think he got into the castle with
his Alps (men)?
The smartest move to catch all of them
and get the holy entrustments...
... is letting him escape from the dungeon.
Now...
Call my best hunter Teokres. Give orders
to him and his men.
This is very dangerous! If Osman gets out
of Teokres' hands...
... it will be impossible to get our hands
on the holy entrustments ever again!
I'd prefer playing this risky game to
be punished....
by Master Yannis, Helen.
Now, do as I say!
Go call Teokres!
Put the barrels next to the others.
The governor's killer's last
meal will be pig soup.
Now that's funny!
Bring me the soup bowl.
A little more.
Put more meat, he should eat it
nicely before dying.
What are you looking at?
Isn't the killer Muslim? He won't
drink that soup.
That's the fun part. Mind your own
business.
There's no getting out of hell for him.
Besides, where else would a Turk go?
Come on, do your job.
Get out.
- Teokres!
- You called me, Helen.
I remember the day Princess Sofia took
your eye out with her one finger.
If you want to keep the other one, listen
to me carefully, Teokres!
If an Alp (man) doesn't care about
the Kayı's honour...
... why would he need a headgear for?
What's the use of a sword if it's not
used for pride, honour.
You don't need those either.
We entrusted our martyr Aybars' fiance...
... and my sister Aygül.
And what did you do?
What did you do? Tell me!
You couldn't protect them.
You didn't hear a thing while my sister
was being kidnapped.
Being a Kayı Alp means to guard
like a hawk!
It means being a warrior who accepts death
for honour!
The one who can't protect entrustments,
who can't protect their honour...
... neither deserves being an Alp, nor
the sword!
But I'll give you what you
deserve, don't you worry.
Dündar Bey, you'd sacrifice yourself and
still wouldn't leave Osman to them.
So why did you?
You can't put an eagle in a cage, Hatun.
It won't fit.
-Tell them, Bamsı Bey.
-Thank you, Dündar Bey.
Zöhre Hatun, if it weren't for Osman, we
wouldn't be here.
He was plotting something, so
I said nothing.
Nonetheless, I'll take precautions.
Bamsı Bey, after all this pain, will we
still be thankful of Osman?
Not only his own but also yours, my
father's, Samsa Bey's, my sister's...
... everyone's life is in danger.
For how long will this go on?
What if he's found guilty in the court?
What if he actually killed the governor?
I don't take any excuses.
I say we make Osman pay for all of this.
Because...
... if Osman's found guilty for the murder
Seljuk Sultan will make us pay for it.
Enough brother, enough!
You never stop praising Osman.
My sister, my father you say but,
Osman sacrificed...
... himself for your sister and your
father!
- Aygül!
- Batur!
Batur is right.
If Osman's found guilty in the court...
... Byzantium won't let this one go.
What if they don't, Dündar Bey? When were
we afraid of Byzantium?
It's not about the Byzantium, Bamsı Bey.
If Byzantium is involved in this, the
Mongolians will also be.
My father must return to his
Tent as soon as possible.
Allah willing, if he comes to terms with
the Sultan in Konya...
... this matter will be sorted out.
- Allah willing!
What is it, didn't you like it? These are
your last meals, Osman Bey.
Enjoy them. The pig inside will
carry you to heaven.
You bastard!
Who entered the dungeon last? Who
entered this dungeon last?
Helen.
Shut the doors, catch Osman.
He will not leave this castle alive!
Sofia...
Mother earth...
Tell me, tell me mother earth.
Is the valiant inside you comfortable?
Is he far from his father, from his Tent?
May our creator not make us
seek help from the cowards.
May your white-haired mother rest
in peace.
Rest in peace.
May your white-haired mother rest
in peace.
Rest in peace.
May my Allah...
never leave you without faith.
Those who say "Amin" may see Allah.
May the hope that Allah gives
you never be given up.
May Allah forgive your sins...
for the sake of Muhammad...
whose name is precious.
My Aybars.
Don't worry about anything, my Aybars.
My Osman will take revenge for you.
My Osman...
will take revenge for you.
You couldn't share the food more unfairly,
brother.
Now...
we're one step closer to the
truth, brothers.
-The tangle will be untangled by the nun.
-Thank you, my Bey, thank you.
Inshaallah, my Bey.
Protect Osman Bey!
Konuralp.
-Salaam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salaam.
Alaikum Salaam.
I learned that you were in the
castle. I came to see you.
I know you're friendly, Konuralp.
If I say that we're going to
die, you'll come anyway.
Come to our table.
With pleasure, my Bey.
Did you do your duty?
Of course, my Bey.
All the castles' private structures in
Vitinya are done, my Bey.
Mashallah.
We have the distance between the walls...
the number of soldiers
who protect the walls...
and the height of the walls.
- We have everyting.
- I am proud of you, Konuralp
Thanks, my Bey.
We'll open the gates of
holy wars again.
And we'll name the lands that we conquer
after the brave conquerors.
Inshaallah, my Bey.
With Allah's permission, the places we
set foot in will be the land...
and those places will be a
magnificent land that...
people shelter.
But first...
we'll take revenge for my brother Aybars.
From now on...
it doesn't matter if
a basilisk we'll confront...
becomes a dragon with seven heads.
Be quiet.
Osman should be here.
We found their traces.
I don't want any crunch. Be careful.
-May it be the cure, father.
-Thanks, daughter.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(in the name of Allah)
We need to find Osman and build a
court before things get crazy.
Or else, they'll stir up
Byzantine and Seljuq...
thinking that he's the killer
of the Governor.
Let's see how much trouble he'll cause.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
Osman Bey got out of the castle
safe and sound, my Bey.
One of his alps let me know.
-Where's Osman's man now?
-He's gone, my Bey.
Batur, if Osman's man is
around, follow him.
Find Osman wherever he is.
Turk friend Yogopolos...
was a huge embarrassment for us.
Kulucahisar is a real
Christian castle now.
They must be around. We'll trap him.
Eternal Allah!
A coyote falls into the wolf's paw!
Who sent you?
Tell me.
Talk to me!
No! Not my eyes!
Stop, stop! No! Not my eyes!
-Not my eyes!
-Talk to me.
Talk and I'll spare your life and eyes.
Stop! Stop, okay! I'll tell you.
-I'll tell you.
-Talk.
I'll tell you! Stop!
Sofia! Sofia!
Princess Sofia!
We'll hide this bastard.
Boran.
Hide him in your secret place.
Okay, my Bey.
My Bey.
Why did Sofia send a man after you?
She knew that I didn't kill
her master, Konuralp.
It's not about me.
It's about the nuns who have
saved me in the bog.
She doesn't know about the nuns, my Bey.
You've just told me.
Whatever the nuns have to do with
her, she thinks that it's about me.
So, she sent her bastards after me.
If we find the nuns...
we'll find the answers of many questions.
We thought that they wouldn't find us
but they came closer to us.
Sir...
-how did they find the treasure?
-We'll learn that from Osman.
Bring him to me.
Master Yannis...
Sofia let Osman escape from the dungeon...
to reach the holy entrustments.
-Who did she send after Osman?
-Teokres, sir.
The most important
teachers in the world...
are the pains.
Now tell me...
where is the...
stolen...
treasure?
Where's Sofia?
She knows that you're here, sir.
She's about to come.
How will we explain this to Master Yannis?
I don't know.
But Master Yannis will be so pissed off.
Where are you going, Sofia?
What are you up to? It's time to find out.
Osman Bey!
Alper!
You shoot too many arrows!
You appear without weapons.
Are you a friend of a foe?
Who are you?
We are the punishers for cruels,
and the helpers for innocents, son.
Our duty is to take you to
what you search for.
Now you masquerade as Turk.
You're so brave, Osman Bey! You've
come all the way for your curiosity.
Not for my curiosity. For my revenge.
Tell me.
Who are you? Why do you hide yourselves?
If you want to find out, come with me.
-Whatever your secret is, tell me now.
-I can't answer your questions.
If you want to know, follow me.
If you don't want the truth,
go to your way.
But we have to go alone.
Tell your men.
They should wait here with Akçaderviş.
My Alps. (men)
Wait here.
Master Yannis...
I couldn't protect the secret, sir.
It's your honor to make me pay the price.
They infiltrated into us, Sofia.
There is a spy in Margalit Monastery.
We should learn who it is.
-How is that possible?
- I came here to take back the holy entrustments.
Not to kill you.
Sofia!
What's happening here?
What are you doing here, Andreas?
You're my most loyal aide. What
the are you doing here?
What's happening in here, Sofia?
Ensheathe your sword.
-I have things to tell you.
-Now!
You'll tell me now!
Right now!
Soldiers!
Arrest Sofia and the rest!
Release your sword, Commander Kalonoz.
Release your sword.
Welcome, Master Nizamettin.
You haven't paid the tribute tax
for a while, Master Hasan.
Tell me, do you deserve this stall?
Do you see this bazaar?
If I don't get tribute taxes on time, how
can I provide a regulation?
I don't need an explanation.
If he doesn't pay his tribute tax
tomorrow, scatter his stall.
He's Osman.
You wanted the truth, Osman Bey.
Here you are.
You're about to learn the truth.
Now you can meet our leader and find
the answers to your questions.
Who's your leader?
Open the door of the secret.
You can see with your eyes.
Who am I meeting?
We're the pilgrims of Allah.
We're told our names as our faith.
People know me as "Edebalı."
Edebalı.
The friend of my father.
The light of Oğuz.
I couldn't get the honor to see your face.
Thank Allah.
A Bey doesn't bow...
before someone, son.
Who's she?
My daughter, Bala Hatun.
The head of sisters.
The girl you see with her
is the friend of my daughter, Gonca.
Master Priest is one of our friends.
He is Tursun.
There are many things that aren't
like the way it seems.
White becomes black...
and black becomes white that...
its mystery is beyond the mind.
Mystery is the work of
wise people like you.
I'm looking for the killers
of my brother Aybars.
I know from my father.
I know you from Kırşehir.
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
We're here...
to blow the Yesevi breath.
To fire the resurrection up, to
flare our tent up...
to build new land.
Do you want to join us...
in this holy way?
I do.
But...
I have a condition.
I want to know all the secrets.
Then, listen to me carefully.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com